
Speaker 1  (00:14)
I'm going to spin-off. 

Speaker 2  (00:25)
I'm 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
I'm going to have them. 

Speaker 2  (00:30)
So shared time to open it. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
This is how it's been done the week. 2 results After that. Like before we had 11 points and like very less points from the last week. 

Speaker 1  (01:23)
So I have done at the starting. This is called like a multi range hedge. I mean, for the last time, we have done hedge feed for one color block, like one color palette. 

Speaker 1  (01:37)
But I change the like, I increased the palette numbers like from the red. I have told you like last week. I have also extracted the pink or any other color palette. 

Speaker 1  (01:50)
So to increase the number of extraction and like, I have in the starting step, we have done like I have done the marphological closing, which means, for example, if we had the red color Okay, if you have this one, the curves we have many lighter in the circles. There is a hallow part, or if it exercle. A circle, sometimes it may not close completely. 

Speaker 1  (02:22)
So we have done the marphological closing, which means it closed the entire part of the line, and so we can get, the more like accurate results. And in that I can choose. 

Speaker 2  (02:37)
The central detection. 

Speaker 1  (02:39)
Yeah, for that morphological, closing is done. So we can increase the number of extraction of this and tried points. And after that, I've done the same thing for even blue mask. 

Speaker 1  (02:52)
But the main major problem is we had many, like it detected the other pixels, like we had the marks in the pixels, so it detected that also, and after that. This is seen for blue. Same thing. 

Speaker 1  (03:12)
Then, for blue, and after that, I have done deluge, like dilution, the dilution which refers to like, if the like, if the morphological closing is done, the white blocks are expanded, and in that if we expand the blocks. So it closes the hallow part of the line or the curve, and it makes sure that if it is having any like tiny segments, it will make sure to connect all those things so we can get in order. And after that. 

Speaker 1  (03:55)
So it's just like we draw. Like, read draw line from the marker so after. But we can't decide which is the centroid point from there and we literally like it scanned the other parts as well. 

Speaker 1  (04:12)
For example, tend to repair something which is in the pixel like it's extracted more pixels. So I have done the noise removal, which removes all the extracted like extra parts from here. You can see that 

Speaker 2  (04:26)
If you can't We're always still talking about cent. 

Speaker 1  (04:32)
Yeah, and like after the noise removal. The extra points, which are here are like deleted from that. And after that, I have done the skeletonization, the skeletonization is nothing. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
But when we have done the morphological, closing and dilution, the white blocks are expanded, so just to get the main points, which keeps the centroid thing. So it deletes the extra part of the like, and it will just it just keeps the middle backbone of the line. 2 Did you understand what I said, okay? 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
For the same line before skeletonization, it gives the dickle line. So if these thicker, we don't get where is this exact centroid points of the H like H points or each center? So I have done the skeletization, so it made the line thinner, and it gives only the centroid points from there. 

Speaker 1  (05:41)
And I have extracted the centroid points, and along with that, there are others to, like other pixels, to I have cleaned it, and we got the theory. Exactly like The right ones, and these are the like, only the right ones and for blue ones I have done this. And after that, of course 

Speaker 2  (06:12)
Today's the skele. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
Yeah, this is before approach the last time we did for like. I wanted to just be bothered and I have increased the points as you said last time, so I did the like I read the skeleton approach for this and we got more points this time. 

Speaker 2  (06:32)
But now the point is, like we've gotten 

Speaker 1  (06:37)
Yeah, sir. This is new thing for me. So I just studied so it has taken like 10. 

Speaker 1  (06:45)
So I just only did this part for like I didn't do much after this. Like, I only get the access and That is what access detection And like Excel Y are detected, and I have a doubt like if you want me to find out the G prime and Earl's, is it fine to detect as an exam y-axis? I can just show you 

Speaker 1  (07:38)
When you gave me the last time initial Datasets. You have given me the CS while it's also in that I just shown as GM Japan like, but for me. When I'm detecting using the algorithms or the code, it is detected as X and Y access to okay And I have done for the red one, but like for doing all these steps, sometimes we just have a few errors when I'm detecting this, like violence nearing all the noise, we just have a very few compared to, but it is more better than this one and just trying to do it again and again, I tried a lot, but I couldn't remove this. 

Speaker 1  (08:31)
So I just need to read more. If you want to work your way 

Speaker 2  (08:37)
Why is it so there's not really a century, right? Because here it looks like the top of the markers. And the bottom of the markers 

Speaker 1  (08:45)
This is because of the curve, which is the right curve. As you see that You have the red curve here, and like this. So it is detected in the same way 

Speaker 2  (08:59)
Okay, so go down and you plot it on top. Just to see, you know, thoughtful comparison 1 to 1 comparison. Did you plot the other one like transparent behind them? 

Speaker 1  (09:13)
I think I need to read like a rerun from the starting. It will take time to want me to merge the picture. So I can merge the picture. 

Speaker 1  (09:24)
I can take the screenshot. 

Speaker 2  (09:28)
Maybe that we're going to mix up for next time. Okay? So maybe to test performance So based on the plot with the original image, this generated ok okay. 

Speaker 1  (09:43)
Tom shut. 

Speaker 2  (09:45)
That way, we can check, right 

Speaker 1  (09:46)
Okay psych I did the 14 points and do 56 points. I just showed you like in the blue mas. Like this, the 14.7 

Speaker 2  (10:01)
I always want to see well, you know if you put one emission on top of the other, how well do they Mat? It's easier to test them. 

Speaker 1  (10:12)
Okay. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (10:13)
So the difference now is that you added this, how it first makes it more diffuse. That brings it. 

Speaker 1  (10:24)
Uh, yes, first is a morphological closing and then delusion, and after that, I have done light noise removal. And after that skeletonization, and this is like scata plotting due to many points are there in the extracted form. We have many scatter plots so I just I don't want to merge it. 

Speaker 1  (10:48)
So I just reduce the points of the red one, and the blue ones are the same. And just working on these to remove even these 2, as will 

Speaker 2  (10:58)
So So this is some matrix, right? 

Speaker 1  (11:04)
Yeah, yeah. Is it fun? Is it fine for this week? 

Speaker 2  (11:18)
If there needs to be some human 

Speaker 1  (11:21)
This is like habit is extracted from the like what is deleted and what is used for the graph like the scatter plot have just taken like is shown for example if you see the sandus are present in this catapult and what is present from the red one is like I just mark the things which we extracted from this image and we used for this cat plots. 

Speaker 2  (11:51)
So is this on top? So this data point, so this is the image. So this is this image plotted on top of the original one. 

Speaker 2  (11:58)
The next 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
Yeah, this part is only plotted in this cataplot. Now Like these are deleted because these are like we have more hallow structures, and like there is no dense values over there. So it is just deleted. 

Speaker 1  (12:15)
And only this much part of the like graph or the pixels used in scater plotting 

Speaker 2  (12:26)
I'm getting a little confused. So this data, yeah, this kind of xy pixel, or these the ones that I'm looking in a different color over there. 

Speaker 1  (12:35)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (12:36)
Okay, so you just overlaying them. Okay? So this is what I want to say. 

Speaker 2  (12:41)
Okay nicely, so you grab this. But this match is really well. I thought it was a matching that. 

Speaker 2  (12:47)
Well, just because of the way it looks, but this is what I wanted to see. So this match has the yellow. The red is matching quite well. 

Speaker 2  (12:56)
And therefore, when I guess looks more smudged. 

Speaker 1  (12:59)
The blue is for the blue line and yellow is for the red line. 

Speaker 2  (13:02)
Great. So there's machine words, just the blue, the cyan is more smudged. Yeah, I guess that's because it's more overlap in the symbols. 

Speaker 2  (13:10)
I see. For example, it's actually matching better than I was worried with the previous blog that found on the MO. 

Speaker 1  (13:17)
Did you guys I was like thinking? How to explain and I know it confuses you a lot like while you're while you see the real image and those cataplats. So I just marked it. 

Speaker 2  (13:33)
But this is just overlaying the same thing. Yeah, so this is good. And, then why doesn't it capture this tail 

Speaker 1  (13:47)
Because it's having more halloweer part and it is not dense as much as these like these points do. So 

Speaker 2  (13:59)
Okay. Is there anything that could be done to capture that or 

Speaker 1  (14:05)
I think I just need to read on moron skeletonization, so I can get this part. 

Speaker 2  (14:12)
But this part is good, so maybe we could. Yeah, I'd say 

Speaker 1  (14:17)
And these are the like xy points, which is extracted from that centroids and Begin. 

Speaker 2  (14:27)
Okay? But in these X 1. 

Speaker 1  (14:30)
This is the same mark as I'm just trying to cut this off. So I didn't read it again. And again? 

Speaker 2  (14:38)
But these are not scaled, right? Because it doesn't know anything about the Axis yet no, it's just yeah, okay. On this word, so maybe So I don't want to okay so For now, I'd say, maybe we're good to continue the access. 

Speaker 2  (14:59)
Okay, scaling and all that stuff. I think we'll come back to see if we can capture more of the hollower symbols, but I think this is good for one to like at this stage. Yeah, so maybe we can shift gears coming for next week. 

Speaker 2  (15:17)
And then you can tell me, what's the strategy for figuring out for the program to figure out the access and scale of the problem, and you know, in that part, if there needs to be some human input, I think you would be fine. I mean, ideally where it is all automated. But you cannot know kind of what you do. 

Speaker 2  (15:40)
Okay. But I'm happy that, yeah, if you go back the ones that you're overlaying the image, you're happy that it captures a lot. Yeah, so it would be nice. 

Speaker 2  (15:48)
Maybe later we could try to reflip, so we're gonna try to find to get the ends. But this is very good and then is there any way to improve so here? Is it capturing still the centroids? 

Speaker 2  (16:00)
Because looking in like very 6 acting Is it captured in the center? So these are just the pixels like 

Speaker 1  (16:07)
It's capturing the centro. 

Speaker 2  (16:09)
So these are all the same 

Speaker 1  (16:10)
Yeah, these are the centroids. This is just the marking of the real image. 

Speaker 2  (16:18)
All right, I see. 

Speaker 1  (16:22)
Centrale just means like the main point, which balances the overall set. If you have a circle where you put the center of the circle is called centroid. So it's the main part of the curve, or the eye. 

Speaker 2  (16:48)
I think for now it's again I just hear they're not really not. All the centers are passing through the metal, right? It's like it's covering some of the edges of the symbols. 

Speaker 2  (16:59)
Yeah, like, for example, here goes kind of down. It's capturing an edge of the symbol. 

Speaker 1  (17:07)
I mean, this is just a marking. And this is a centroid. Okay, you mean okay yeah. 

Speaker 2  (17:15)
By exploring down the data doesn't really go down like this, right. Yeah, it's probably capturing the symbol, like the edge of the symbols and some way So I think that we could try to refine that later. But now maybe let's tackle the Axis. 

Speaker 2  (17:30)
Because even in a tool like this I guess it's still kind of a rough and ready stage, but even this would be helpful in terms of some of the analysis that we do. What I do. It'd be hard to you know. 

Speaker 2  (17:46)
It was not really speaking out specific data points, it would be hard to show it in publication or something like that. But for some of the analysis that we do even having something like this is useful. So so I think, you know, if you can think of strategies to improve this, right, so to capture kind of a smoother trend of the symbols. 

Speaker 2  (18:10)
Think about what strategies we could do. But for now, I think it's okay to move to the next station. Work on the action. 

Speaker 2  (18:18)
There will circle back if there's time. And then you know, the semester goes through it will circle back and see if there's some refinement that can be done. Never, let's go slipping, good Okay so for the access you mentioned, you're going to use 

Speaker 1  (18:34)
Transformers, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (18:38)
And then right here, you know how the goal right is that it'll recognize the scale, right? Sometimes we have log log scales, so this one is log lo. 

Speaker 1  (18:48)
No kid. 

Speaker 2  (18:49)
Sometimes it's linear scale. I'm not sure that something that needs to be inputted or if the program would capture that itself either way, we're swimming right? Specifying log Axis is easy for like a user to do. 

Speaker 2  (19:05)
Yeah, so let's discuss that next week. Like, what strategy we could use and you know, if a user needs to input, whether it's log, we know which acts or which axes logarithmically scale. I think that's fine, still okay. 

Speaker 2  (19:20)
I'm user intervention. 

Speaker 1  (19:27)
I'll try my best to do. I'm sorry if you're finding this is very small work that I'm doing. I'm very sorry for that. 

Speaker 1  (19:36)
I'm just traveling in a like, I'm just doing trial-and-error so if you find it out very less book 4 than hers, I'm very sorry for that. 

Speaker 2  (19:45)
Oh, no, no, no I mean And we were stud from 0, so it is very good. I think you know it's 10 hours a week is also like not. You know, I really expect you to plan like 40 or something like that. 

Speaker 2  (20:01)
This is, I think it's very appropriate for the, you know, for the amount of time and the task, and I think it's good progress. Okay, so 

Speaker 1  (20:10)
And I'm very thankful to you. I'm learning new things as well. Because of your skills. 

Speaker 2  (20:16)
Now definitely uploading a lot too here. Because I love these techniques that I wasn't familiar with them. But this is good. 

Speaker 2  (20:25)
Yeah. So I think kind of four now kind of the status I would say is with the data identifying well probably I want us to go back to it to try to refine it but I think for now, it's good. And then we can focus on the access for a while. 

Speaker 2  (20:40)
And hopefully if we get the access to work, well, we can then and hopefully there's enough time to still go back in the semester to still go back to see if there's a refinery, we can do to capture also at this stage. You can also test that out to test out the same procedure with a different setup. 

Speaker 1  (20:58)
And sure I'll do that with 

Speaker 2  (21:00)
Pick one with a linear access, so there are some data that is not as busy, right. So this is kind of a tough slot, right? Because all the symbols are as much together. 

Speaker 2  (21:09)
I think some of the sample data that I send you. Some of the plots have the data move 

Speaker 1  (21:15)
More stuff yeah. 

Speaker 2  (21:17)
I'm tried on one of those. Sometimes works, but it also teaches help us figure out what, you know. It's always trying to hear when or some weak points in the current protocol or something like that. 

Speaker 2  (21:31)
Okay yeah. But it's looking good. So then so then for next week, I'd say, let's focus more on the Axis, and then we'll just have that as a reminder make a note somewhere that we want to circle back to see. 

Speaker 2  (21:46)
If we can refine this map 

Speaker 1  (21:49)
Okay? First and try for the next data set as you said. For the linear, or like log lock, I'll change the data. 

Speaker 1  (21:56)
And I'll check and along with that. I'll work on this as well like for this Datasets. And I'll see like how much work can we do done for the next 

Speaker 2  (22:07)
That sounds good. Good morning, questioning the question. 

Speaker 1  (22:13)
And the whackage How do we do weekend? If possible, are you free on Thursday? Then, Wednesdays like Thursday afternoon. 

Speaker 2  (22:28)
Also, you want to change, and you're watching it. 

Speaker 1  (22:33)
You know because dad can never dispose of that 2 or 2 dates before. So only if you're open 

Speaker 2  (22:44)
Yeah, this joint. So, last week we did Thursday's 230 to 30. So I want to keep that time, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (22:56)
If I said next so what we're going to do is, I'm going to move it. So So I'm gonna do a bit here now. But next week. 

Speaker 2  (23:12)
I won't be able to meet because I'm doing interviews graduate student. 

Speaker 2  (23:37)
So Thursday, sorry. It was just 

Speaker 2  (24:12)
So I changed all of them to Thursdays at 230 next week. I won't be able to meet on Thursday, so we can either do an email update so you can tell me kind of how progress was, and then we can make the week after mission, or we could try to meet a different time through question. 

Speaker 1  (24:31)
I can even do I can commit and meet up you at the same time. 

Speaker 2  (24:39)
Okay. So how about this for next week? Because I'll also be catching up with some stuff. 

Speaker 2  (24:46)
I'm gonna cancel the meeting next week. But we want to meet. Just let me know. 

Speaker 2  (24:50)
Okay. And then. So our next meeting unless you send me start message for email Unless you Come on, so Yeah, so our next meeting will be the 20:06 for next week on Thursday. 

Speaker 2  (25:06)
You send me an email with another. I'll put it in the calendar. 
