
Speaker 1  (00:07)
Okay. So I guess everything's normal. I did any updates involved with the same thing or everything good. 

Speaker 2  (00:22)
Yeah, everything is good. And I just like checked what you have said, and based on that, like, till I'm graduating in me. So before me, I wanted to like, finish this project. 

Speaker 2  (00:37)
So I just divided the project into whole, like 1010 hairs each till the last week. And along with that, what are the technical approaches we are doing? 

Speaker 1  (00:51)
Yep, that's good. So how long gotta look at the schedule? 

Speaker 2  (00:55)
Yeah, let me show you. I can even start from today. Because I don't have any work today tomorrow and I didn't work this week. 

Speaker 2  (01:05)
So I can work on that. And like the week it counts like from Thursday to Wednesday. Yeah, and I just want to know when there will be the weekly meetings with you. 

Speaker 1  (01:23)
We can keep it at this time or we can put it on Thursday. 

Speaker 2  (01:27)
I'll be like I have another work on Thursday and Friday. I just work on me 2 days, so 1 day I have plazas on Friday and Thursday. I have work. 

Speaker 2  (01:39)
So if we can work on like, if we can meet any other day from Monday to Wednesday it will be fine. 

Speaker 1  (01:48)
Let's find a schedule. We could do it. What we'll do with Wednesdays okay. 

Speaker 1  (02:05)
Wednesdays of this time, well, not this time. 101 days at 10 assure you okay, so I'll just create a new meeting time, okay. Also, I'm Wednesday's at 10 AM. 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
Then, I'll send you a recurring meeting so we have this lot. I mean, you don't so things happen, and we sometimes we'll need to reschedule, but that keeps 

Speaker 2  (02:34)
For this week work? What can I do for tomorrow? Will there repeat again? 

Speaker 1  (02:41)
So let's scholars today's dispute meeting 

Speaker 2  (02:45)
Sheriff said, and based on the things you send, I felt like for this week, I just want to create as you said, we can create the Google collab work that we have done. And if you're okay to put that on the GitHub, we can create the repository based on it. So if I do anything I can pull it on the GitHub, so you can access it too. 

Speaker 2  (03:09)
And we can make it private or public. If you as it, you wish 

Speaker 1  (03:14)
The for nanographic help, if you can put me as a so Google club, you can put multiple owners right to log. 

Speaker 2  (03:23)
Yes, sir. 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
And I don't even give hubs the same way you can have multiple nurs. Can you I us keep a while ago? But I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (03:32)
I guess sir. I can do that public. 

Speaker 1  (03:35)
But maybe put it private, and then 

Speaker 2  (03:37)
Yeah, I can do the private because I know it's confidential yeah. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
We may decide to change it later, but we're down, let's just keep everything pri. But if you're going to put me as coal over, that'd be good. 

Speaker 2  (03:52)
There it is and berries don't that like for the next weeks? Analyzing the sample images that you have sent first I need to like. Yes, we need to do the coding part. 

Speaker 2  (04:04)
So after that, we can analyze the images that you have sun. And after that weeks, we can even like build, like, we can collect more images or Datasets from the as I said before from the websites. Or if you're doing any work, if you have any images, you can send it to me. 

Speaker 2  (04:21)
I just want to need to know like where we can contact each other. Like mail or the teams. Anything would be. 

Speaker 1  (04:31)
So I can add you to this slack. Okay, let's see. 

Speaker 1  (04:48)
Forget how to do these things. Oh, that was something that's Anyway, I allowed you to this lock to remember how to Send that on invitation I'm going to add you to the group channel. Now I'll do it later. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
I should all send you a slack. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (05:27)
1 week, we just need to like completely work on the datas because we just need to like we need to convert the Datasets. If in case we have images, we need just need to convert into grayscale, because we can get the clarity about the image like in the coding. If we change it to the grayscale, we can get the clear image with the pixels better than colorful images, so we can do that on the one weeks. 

Speaker 2  (05:54)
And like rest of the weeks, I have just divided and I just need some like detailed technologies which we can use for the coding I use the primary like python as I said and open CVS are like we just need to further detection process and numb free means for numerical plotting anything for numerical plotting and even pandas too, and for map plot, lip means which is based for like XY plots which we make we use the mathematical terms. So for that, we need the math lip and Google collabs. As I said for the coding and spirit, images is like image processing for further image like anything we need to do with the images we can use it. 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
And this is how we do the process 

Speaker 1  (06:50)
Okay, here we go up. Just go up a little bit. So what's the difference between psychic and open TV? 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
I'm sorry difference between psychit image and an open CV. 

Speaker 2  (07:03)
Open savvy means the imports and the Transformers which means, for example, for another project. I have used like Hugging Face which we can with the speech into text. For this for anything which we need to change is like from image to any text formation or something we can do that. 

Speaker 2  (07:25)
But the open CV, whereas the skirt image is like it's an optional thing we can do like. Advanced filtering in the open sea V in which we can like if we have 15 features based on that, which feature is the best we can filter it using skeleton mages. 

Speaker 1  (07:48)
To psychiatrist. In python, and then opencv slowly priests set of 

Speaker 2  (08:01)
Transformer, oh yes, sir, yes. 

Speaker 1  (08:04)
Pretrained. Okay, they're both open source. I mean, open source but open C open source 

Speaker 2  (08:14)
And I just have the questions about. Yes, sir. Like it just used for another kind of project. 

Speaker 2  (08:22)
Not for this, and I just want to know about accuracy level. Like what is the plus or minus that you accept for your work? 

Speaker 1  (08:35)
So that is something we'll assess It's kind of as we go okay. I mainly wanted to be more accurate than a human. 

Speaker 2  (08:44)
So yeah. Like, I'm in the ones. 

Speaker 1  (08:49)
So I mean, I'm guessing it would depend right? And again, this is something that we can refine where you're say you're taking an image if we can let's say right for each image. A pixel means different things right? 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
Because sometimes you have log log plots that are orders of magnitude. Sometimes you have linear linear plots which, you know, may give you point something accuracy. I'd say for now if we can just see that it's getting, you know, reasonable accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (09:24)
And by reasonable, I mean that When we extract the data, we can say by hand validated and checked that the numbers agree with what you can see by high. That's fine. And then after that, once we get that set off, if we can find a way to convert the pixel resolution to a numerical resolution that tend to 

Speaker 2  (09:48)
Yes, I got 

Speaker 1  (09:50)
We're not a great but a really good because then we have very accurate tool. But for now, I'd say, let's first just get a working tool. And yeah, I'd say the accuracy I'm guessing the resolutions. 

Speaker 1  (10:04)
The minimum the maximum accuracy is determined by a pixel. Okay? So if we can convert that say, how many This error estimation, we have from the pixel to what it translates numerically, then that we value it. 

Speaker 2  (10:20)
And what kind of graph would you prefer like? Is it the what kind of plot do you prefer? Is it like line graph or 

Speaker 1  (10:30)
I'm sorry scatter plot, okay. We'll focus on scatter plots cause I want this tool to be able to gather experimental data from the literature right? We take a paper instead. 

Speaker 1  (10:41)
I'll do sets of data having to like point them in have something that works very well for this particular type of data. Okay so no matter who can expand that later. But for now. 

Speaker 1  (10:54)
The, you know, it works very well then. Let's say, you know, you take a SnapShot, chug it through the pipeline. Then, at the end, you're gonna see SB file with very good data for that graph. 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
And mostly scatter plots, and then's the Priority after we deal with scatter plots, then we can think of extension. 

Speaker 2  (11:22)
Can you tell me in which stage you are in the project or 

Speaker 1  (11:25)
This is completely starting. 

Speaker 2  (11:28)
So 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
Yeah, so the science part of this project is more that I want to do a review article with a lot of the experimental data that's been published. But it's very time consuming to be picking out points. So that's where this tool I wanted to come in. 

Speaker 1  (11:46)
Okay. And then I wanted to be usable and friendly enough. That a new graduate student say, width of some basic python background, could grab a copy and use it right 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
Okay, sure. 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
So Yeah, so that's essentially what I'm hoping comes out of these 2, so it's more like a very applied project. And yeah, so no one I had an undergraduate student. I asked to assess what tools were available? 

Speaker 1  (12:20)
I mean, I'm not sure to what extent he'd dug into it. Because his chemistry student, he was in Computer Science. But there didn't seem, I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (12:31)
There's, for example, there's this plot digitizer app. That kind of does it kind of does it that you can upload? They have an online tool. 

Speaker 1  (12:42)
You upload an image and you kind of select a portion and it'll try to pick out a data point when I try to work that well. 

Speaker 2  (12:52)
I can try it if you want. 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
So you can assess sort of really so the way I want to do this project is It's very practical. I want the studio tool that can be used by graduate students. Undergraduate students and the main purpose of the tool right? 

Speaker 1  (13:11)
And I wanted to be kind of open source without open source without my group doesn't have to pay some sort of subscription to anything. Yeah, just something that's robust that can take us scatter plot from an image in a published article And extract the Axis, right and extract Scaling up the accent. And then extract the data points and I'll put ACS B file with those data points. 

Speaker 1  (13:44)
That way, I have a very simple X and Y plot X and Y Datasets that then I can make a new plot with. That's when compile large amounts of data? Yeah, so there's not really anyone has done it in my group. 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
I imagine that, you know, there may be some companies that have done stuff like this. Already, it seems reasonable. I just want a reliable tool that my group can use. 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
And that specialized to scatter plots, and I'm guessing, in, the more you specialize at the AC. It is so we can initially specialize also through reality data. Which very often the features are that is viscoastic, modulus and loss modulus, and that is, in a log log plot. 

Speaker 1  (14:37)
Design answer your question. So we're essentially starting from 0. 

Speaker 2  (14:41)
That's like questions if I missed anything and asked. 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
Did you have any like other research assistant which I need to contact for any other information or am I the only mandator? 

Speaker 1  (15:45)
You're right now. I have one graduate student. She doesn't work in this reallogy project. 

Speaker 1  (15:51)
She doesn't do a different project. Okay. It's mostly you and me candidates soon. 

Speaker 1  (16:01)
Maybe I'll start doing some word meetings that basically would be you and her Looks for now. I think you know on your main point of contact. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (16:10)
Did you look here on separate? Animal project. Yeah, eventually it would be nice to extend this to 2, you know, analyze plus that show up often in her research. 

Speaker 1  (16:24)
But I want to, you know, compartmentalize, we can do that after we get something that works for this reality stuff because that's the one thing. But the funding is coming from a reality. So I want to make this tool work with reality data interest. 

Speaker 1  (16:41)
Yeah, so now right now, but eventually what we may do is we'll have our individual meeting. And maybe either once every two weeks or once a month, we'll have a good meeting. No, yeah, and then we'll discuss what we can talk about meeting. 

Speaker 1  (16:57)
I can't get my enthusiastic graduate student in chemical engineering. So you're applying to graduate school your master's students, you're more going to be looking for jobs. Yeah, so you know, interest kind of like the paths. 

Speaker 1  (17:10)
Several different I think in terms of how this could work for you, right? The faster we get a tool working right, the faster you can kind of have it in your CV and examine GM as a reference. And how big of your reference? 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
And then write as an semester goes on and we get a working tool. We can assess something you can tell me. I don't know How Thing's work in Computer Science like job market if making the cool public you know. 

Speaker 2  (17:41)
It's different for international students here. 

Speaker 1  (17:47)
But I've heard that sometimes Computer Science, you want come your projects to be the repository we've been published. So that employers can check on my so, you know, I'm open to that later right since this tool. This tool I wanted to gather beta. 

Speaker 1  (18:03)
It's not like a proprietary research. And I would imagine that some companies already have a version of this. You know, pay for whatever I haven't looked in detail, but right? 

Speaker 1  (18:17)
So if later on right? It would be good for your job. Search to make it public. 

Speaker 1  (18:25)
And open to it and we can talk about it as well as to get something working first I always like to have you know, the private version that you know has blogs. 

Speaker 2  (18:36)
What would be better like 

Speaker 1  (18:38)
And once we have something that works very well then. We put it up and maybe we'll have like a private version of you know, extending. And then a more limited public version that just has one 

Speaker 2  (18:48)
I know incredib. 

Speaker 1  (18:50)
And I fine with that, you know I'm probably too good for you job search. If we have something public, you know, in a public report story. But I'd like us to get something working first. 

Speaker 1  (19:04)
Yeah, so for now, we'll mostly be you. And me. So I'm gonna have a student yet working and reallogy stuff. 

Speaker 1  (19:13)
And then we may do some group meetings that we also get to meet and doesn't remember 2 groups be out. And that will mostly be doing our weekly meeting going through progress. So the way I like to do weekly meetings is Here we go. 

Speaker 1  (19:31)
You can give me an update of what you've been doing. What's the status of things? And then I'll start asking questions. 

Speaker 1  (19:37)
Okay, now typically, I ask student science questions, right? But one thing that I'm going to be asking you a lot is how do you solve algorithms work? Okay? 

Speaker 1  (19:47)
Because so I am half a general sense of the math behind neural networks. And all these, you know, different machine learning and AI methods, but I haven't really had time to apply them in practice. So I'm gonna be asking you, okay mostly from the theories. 

Speaker 1  (20:08)
Because that's what I meant, okay. 

Speaker 2  (20:11)
And it'll be good to know the theory before, like black girls. 

Speaker 1  (20:15)
Right, so I'm with you. My research is a lot of theory. So I've been reading a little bit more about, you know, AI machine learning methods like the math behind it. 

Speaker 1  (20:26)
But I hadn't really had time to do some practice. So, I'm gonna You know, where did this part come in? And where did that sprint coming? 

Speaker 2  (20:34)
There will be helpful for me too. 

Speaker 1  (20:37)
So this often healthier how meanings will go, and if you don't know something that's fine. I probably do. Is like okay, please undoubtedly. 

Speaker 1  (20:46)
We can talk about it because I Don' Yeah, so those are the main things that's kind of the format of the meetings then just good that you're going to schedule. So maybe when you share the Google lab and stuff, have that schedule in, and then I mean, you go in and make some suggestions different priorities. Okay, do you have any other questions? 

Speaker 2  (21:14)
Nothing for now. 

Speaker 1  (21:18)
Yeah, so how about then we talk about this coming week? So once the plan for this coming week, what do you envision? 

Speaker 2  (21:25)
Yes, for 2 days like I'll just set up the I've set up everything. And for the next I'll or else I'll send you the details which I can do for the next 2 week before I start the work. And like you'll get the details about it and begin 

Speaker 1  (21:45)
So you want to okay so again you want to share when you share Google app and you have propository, just gonna share the schedule. Yes, okay, and then I'll look into it. As if the first thing I mean, I would imagine right here. 

Speaker 1  (22:03)
I'll ask you because I haven't worked with this image processing stuff before. I would say, have a control, right, have like, have an image that you extract the data. Yourself by hand. 

Speaker 1  (22:19)
And then word has worked with that as a control. So Now as you start setting things up, I guess I'll always like to have you know. Validated data. 

Speaker 1  (22:34)
Yeah, so have say at least a few 1 or 2 images. That you extracted the data, yourself or some And that you know is right? 2 random 2 dwelling tests here. 

Speaker 2  (22:53)
Yes, yes, sir. 

Speaker 1  (22:56)
I think some of the stuff that I shared with me already. 

Speaker 2  (22:58)
Yeah, I do have that okay. 

Speaker 1  (23:05)
Yeah, other than that. I guess I'll just look at your schedule because yeah, I haven't really worked with image processing or so. I'm i'm As much of the coating as possible. 

Speaker 1  (23:18)
Yeah, please do it a python because, yes Other than that, I think that covers, I mean 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
Back and we can do python, but for friend Henry. We just need the hdml, like to make the bashboards or something. We need to do HTML for your information. 

Speaker 1  (23:42)
All you mean to do like A 

Speaker 2  (23:44)
Cool cooling. Oh yeah, okay. How the dashboard works from one of my projects? 

Speaker 1  (23:54)
That's it for now, let's just focus on 

Speaker 2  (23:58)
I can say. 

Speaker 1  (23:59)
Okay? And you know, if this is so I have a lot of tools. I don't know that I just used a terminal and I'll tell you, okay, run this script. 

Speaker 1  (24:09)
And this data set. So for now, if we can get something that works without a front end. 

Speaker 2  (24:15)
No, because first 

Speaker 1  (24:17)
Okay more more initially, I'm more interested in you know getting something that works. The link is high quality. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (24:26)
And that is easy to validate, right? There yeah, let's say I don't know how we could do this. But There's a way to automatically make a plot from the extracted data. 

Speaker 1  (24:37)
We make the program shortly side by side images. So you can very quickly check. Yeah, that'll be really nice. 

Speaker 1  (24:46)
Front and wise. All of our students need to learn to use a terminal. So, you know, if it's, if it's very like, you know, if, for now I'm not so concerned about the film having who we are doing oh kids. 

Speaker 1  (25:00)
I swear I'm getting something robust that works. And you know, initially, we can just run in the terminal, but I can just call the Pi script, feed it a bunch of images, over 1 of 2 images, and that very quickly. I can you know gives me the data gives me the original image and I can check can validity the next 1 next 1 next 1. 

Speaker 1  (25:22)
Let's not forget, about the front end right now Just focus on the back end and need something accurate robust. And then, after that, you know, based on where we are at, we can, of course, do a front end, do other things to make 

Speaker 2  (25:39)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (25:41)
Yeah, so in a way, maybe kind of expectation kind of your customers will be like me. May leave me and my graduate students. They all know python, or they all are python. 

Speaker 1  (25:55)
If they don't know it yet that they will know to some degree, they may learn C or 4 Trin, but mostly they'll be working on python. Okay. And they should become, they will all be comfortable with legs right with another next terminal. 

Speaker 1  (26:11)
Because that's what they're using the cluster. So so long as we have something that's usable with that. You know, understand that. 

Speaker 2  (26:19)
Is there a high 

Speaker 1  (26:23)
I'm more interested in being accurate and reliable. Let's say after we got something accurate and reliable. That runs on the terminal, then we can focus on the front. 

Speaker 2  (26:33)
That's pictures, okay. 

Speaker 1  (26:36)
I'm not as worried about the front end right now. We'll bring that in later. So I'm very question for you is kind of how Based on your experience before Is this a tool that should be easy domain? 

Speaker 1  (26:55)
That should take longer domain. What is your impression 

Speaker 2  (27:00)
Based like If we consider the hearts which I work on like we can do within a month or 3 months. It may take up to like 1 to 1 and a 1 months, we can do that. But if we need like it completely based on the data which we are using the amount of data her. 

Speaker 2  (27:22)
If we are using more than like we can train the images, as you said, it depends completely depends on how many image we have training and testing. So 

Speaker 1  (27:37)
It's totally, I mean. But why would it depend and how many English per billion testing? Do you mean the time frame? 

Speaker 2  (27:45)
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Um, like for building the 2 for building any projects, it may mean like 11 and a 1 month. 

Speaker 2  (27:55)
If it is, if the amount of data is Uh what to say. If it's like the little bit, it completely depends on how much data we are using. And how much need you need like for accuracy? 

Speaker 2  (28:13)
And it depends on errors as well. So 

Speaker 1  (28:19)
It was obviously so. Yeah, I guess this just gets started because other than all this done better. Once I start seeing you know what parts are being coated. 

Speaker 1  (28:32)
Yeah, what parts are block boxed? So in your previous project that you have image processing I'm guessing so gradually write a main script that is calling all the python 2 rules. Is it like an object? 

Speaker 1  (28:54)
So the image processing part that is supposed to extract the data 

Speaker 2  (28:59)
I think you'll see as we fall yeah. 

Speaker 1  (29:01)
That's like a python option. 

Speaker 2  (29:03)
Yes, it's on feature engineering. We call it as feature engineering, which means like the complete extraction of the data and conversion into any graphs, which, like which will be based on this. 

Speaker 1  (29:21)
Okay, so I'm guessing it first extracts. The pixels yeah, so Excel extracts pixel data. Yeah, these pixel data like what's deranged, is 0 to 1 number or You see you shoot like an audit. 

Speaker 2  (29:37)
The image that azaric started in the form of zeros and ones, which are binaries, but we need to convert into LGBT grayscale, to get the first we change the colors from LGBT grayscale, and after that, we extract the datas in the form of binary, and we like we collect the details about it, and we can plot the graphs after that. 

Speaker 1  (30:04)
Okay. So I guess in terms of like a flow short. You gotta look at an image, convert it to grayscale. 

Speaker 1  (30:14)
Yeah And after that, same makes a numerical 011, say, 0 being black, one being black cold. And then from there 

Speaker 2  (30:31)
And we can do confusion matrix as well. The Matrix which makes like if we do The Matrix it will be easier for us to identify where are the errors and the main part which it shows if it is a 0 or it will be in the form of numbers I can show you like we are doing the code. It would be helpful if I have any 

Speaker 1  (30:58)
So this is the type of questions that I'll be asking a little bit about what's happening in the background. Because if we want to know how the tool works. There's a water module. 

Speaker 1  (31:08)
Now, with this Alright. You're extracted image, you slide a kid to turn it to grayscale, then you turn the image into some numerical, right? And you start with a matrix right? 

Speaker 1  (31:19)
The element is pixel each one element and 01 for black versus X. Yeah And from there, that matrix needs to be translated to an Axis, and then to points. Yeah, and what type of operation. 

Speaker 1  (31:35)
And that's the part where open CV comes in awe. 

Speaker 2  (31:39)
Before that, during importing importing any of the libraries which we need for coding part 

Speaker 1  (31:47)
Okay. And then to solve All right, so I'll ask more next time. Because it's just unclear to me. 

Speaker 1  (32:02)
So everything that we just talked about, I would imagine trying to do just with python, because python has functions for image processing We've turned in things to books. Yeah, so why would we need open CV? 

Speaker 2  (32:17)
For before feature engineering, we need to import the data like import the libraries for coding like where the coding works. So I can say before feature engineering sharing. 

Speaker 1  (32:32)
So let's see what is the suppy total took it? 

Speaker 2  (32:36)
Yeah, uh, yes, sir. 

Speaker 1  (32:41)
Yeah, so really python is using open cd function. Do we airport damage transform it? And then you get a matrix with an element And that's where I'm guessing that the features 

Speaker 2  (33:00)
Yeah, right, isser. 

Speaker 1  (33:03)
The water range sprint, I've done mansion. 

Speaker 2  (33:06)
And if they have, for example, if you have any molecular nanomolecules, if it contains many features, if you want any in like, if you want one of the best features out of it, we can do that during feature engineering. 

Speaker 1  (33:25)
Do I want to say a feature engineering? What whatever you do doing. 

Speaker 2  (33:28)
And like if you have any top 15 features, for example, if you need to pick any of the feature out of it, we can do that during the feature engineering process. 

Speaker 1  (33:41)
You know, I mean but so by feature, you mean The Matrix or like human identifiable eigenvalue item? 

Speaker 2  (33:49)
Just a second. So let me show you 2, but 

Speaker 2  (34:05)
I got it. I missed it, so we okay? 

Speaker 2  (34:33)
This is one of the models which we had, I have trained for another project. These are the 15 features or 20 features which listed like to detect the best attack type. So in it we like I have taken the dsd bites because it have more accuracy than any other things we can do that in feature. 

Speaker 2  (34:56)
This is the feature engineering plan. 

Speaker 1  (34:58)
Okay, so what is dsd bites? So these are features 

Speaker 2  (35:02)
Yes, these are the number of bites which send from the source to destination. 

Speaker 1  (35:08)
These are features of the beta. Yeah. So but in an image, the features would be 

Speaker 2  (35:14)
And this will be the confusion matrix, which we can like before doing any of the graphs, which we can do that based on classes. We can divide into classes and like after this, we can get the graphs easily. It will be better with better accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (35:34)
Okay, so let's go back to the features. So in an image We have an image that was translating to a matrix of pixels with album 0 and 1 features would be what column. Numbers of zeros numbers of one inch column, one would be the features of that matrix. 

Speaker 2  (35:57)
This is not for image processing. This is completely based on other like these data. Based on The attack detection on IoT platforms, and if we take the images, it is same as like this. 

Speaker 2  (36:14)
Maybe it comes, and after that I told you to, like, after conversion into our gp 2 grayscale, we can extract those. You are saying about the binary things which we extract after image processing. 

Speaker 1  (36:31)
Greta, mcgur. Brazil, I'm trying to understand what would be the features that we're trained for. 

Speaker 2  (36:38)
Okay? Okay, uh. 

Speaker 1  (36:39)
So we have an image right? So let's say it's an object. We're turning to grayscale, we've translated into zeros and ones. 

Speaker 1  (36:48)
Yes, I mean, this would be just like A N by N matrix with each pixel, okay, 01 right? So when you say feature engineering, I'm thinking, are we looking for features of this matrix? Yes, yeah, essentially. 

Speaker 2  (37:05)
And yes, sir. 

Speaker 1  (37:09)
So the features which is, you know. So we would have to start picking out what features of this matrix are we trained for yeah? 

Speaker 2  (37:17)
I'm sorry, and for example, I have done image processing one like for unhelp bases it. I have one image of it based on cancerous cells. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (37:30)
If you have the image of blood clots or blood cells. It contains cancerous cells in which it converts the image into LGBT grayscale, in that image where the dense part of the cells are there it is taken as one of like it is taken as one, and the parts are taken as 0. And those one I have mentioned you, as one, right? 

Speaker 2  (37:56)
Those are taken as a features. In which, if it takes 2 dense, it is called type 4 cancer and type 3 type 2 like stages, stage 1 stage 2 stage 3. Based on that, and like, we have divided into stage one stage, 2 and stage 3 and stage 4. 

Speaker 1  (38:19)
So, feature here is a feature of the translator yes of the image translate. 

Speaker 2  (38:24)
Yeah, sir. 

Speaker 1  (38:26)
The circuit sounds good. So I'm guessing we'll be thinking of features as I don't know numbers of ones in a column numbers of one in a row. And close during what those into particular subsequents of The Matrix Yeah, I could see how so In featuring engineering, that's what you're mean. 

Speaker 1  (38:51)
We're going to look at Aspects yesterday yesterday. 

Speaker 2  (38:58)
That would be good for like plotting that as anxiet. In Duo, graphs. 

Speaker 1  (39:04)
Well, I mean, I'm, I'm guessing for deciding what's a data point. Talks so, this one I'm trying to get out of here. And you're going to tell me if I'm misunderstanding okay? 

Speaker 1  (39:47)
Alright, so Do you have any image? Wipe pandg. This gets fed to Grayscale, turning rights convert to gradescale. 

Speaker 1  (40:08)
All right, and when this gets translated To a matrix. Good luck. Among these are pixels Populated by zeros and So typically there's an access, so I'm guessing there'll be a rule of once. 

Speaker 2  (40:31)
Alright, okay. 

Speaker 1  (40:34)
Why and x-axis? So this should be rows of ones. And then We'll have your symbols right? 

Speaker 1  (40:44)
Yes, sometimes within the same Don't want to say feature engineering, do essentially saying yet. So these are the features we have to be looking at the numbers of ones in a row. We pick out what features we want. 

Speaker 2  (40:59)
Like Okay? If this is The Matrix as I said, it contains once and zeros along with many number of like many numbers, it means this is the best features. It will select these features and be like we can do. 

Speaker 2  (41:20)
We can. I'm sorry based on these features. We can plot the graph after knowing the best feature out of it. 

Speaker 2  (41:32)
So it depends on you as well if you want any changes during the project you can tell me so I can work on it. 

Speaker 1  (41:40)
I'll grab soon in terms of when you say features. I guess what I'm asking is what are the features like exactly what is? What are we defining? 

Speaker 1  (41:48)
As features, is that something that you determined? You kind of look for 

Speaker 2  (41:53)
Yes, based on like I thought, the molecules must have some on the project with you are doing. Obviously you'll select one of the molecules which is best. And like, have, for example, how they say that. 

Speaker 2  (42:17)
If you have a bunch of the molecules or something, how will you extract the best out of it? It depends on that we can do the features, and if I just need to study on the molecules. Because I don't remember all those things before what I have studied. 

Speaker 2  (42:36)
And I'll send it to you if you feel it is not all it does. 

Speaker 1  (42:43)
So for now, I don't think we need to work anything about molecules. We're just looking at plots. So scatter plots from which we just want to be able to identify different symbols, and then turn that into Datasets. 

Speaker 1  (42:59)
Okay. So I'm going to set so okay. So Sometimes like features is something you can decide, right? 

Speaker 1  (43:09)
It's kind of like you decide. What is the feature? And what is training is it's All right, so maybe I start. 

Speaker 1  (43:17)
We can just talk about what features you're picking on this data. It seems to me like the aren't that many features? Because if you if we have a plot that is essentially an image pixel image that turns the grayscale. 

Speaker 1  (43:33)
But then you just have a and by N matrix with ones and zeros. I mean. Well, what would be a feature would be an element number of wants in a row number of ones in a column. 

Speaker 1  (43:48)
I don't maybe proximity, maybe like new neighbors. Let's say I have a pixel here, dozens neighborhouse, 0 or 1 is, are those type of questions works well. 

Speaker 2  (43:57)
Yes, I like. Maybe you're talking about the cannier, snipers like that. 

Speaker 1  (44:04)
Here I'm just trying to understand What feature of an And by endangering, could you remind them could pick up data points, right? 

Speaker 2  (44:16)
Can we study about the and let me clarify you in the next meeting? 

Speaker 1  (44:22)
And so these are the things that I'll be asking meaning, because I really want to understand how this algorithm works. That's one of the reasons why I do. This is kind of to introduce myself to this machine learning AI stuff in practice. 

Speaker 1  (44:38)
Okay? But yeah, so kind of what I'm seeing what I'm hearing is okay, turning an image to Gray school. We just use some python function, right? 

Speaker 1  (44:48)
Turning to the grayscale image into an environ matrix. That's just pixels, right? That's just a python function. 

Speaker 1  (44:55)
The alternative things into an N by N matrix. With each element being a pixel I'm guessing that the next part is then really the bulk of the project, right? 

Speaker 2  (45:09)
Once the church of yesterday 

Speaker 1  (45:12)
Tell you where are the axes and where are 

Speaker 2  (45:17)
We can get it like during the training training of the images If you have lads, number of data set, it will train 80% of the data set into like, you'll test the 80% of the train, 80% of the data set. And test 20% of the data set based on it. You'll collect the features I'll let you in. 

Speaker 2  (45:39)
By next week, because I'll get the clarity too. It will be healthy for 

Speaker 1  (45:43)
Yeah, yeah, so a couple of things that I'll ask you about next week. Okay, is this features? So what features are we picking? 

Speaker 1  (45:50)
So okay? And second is, you know, when we train, what exactly are we doing? And how are we training, right? 

Speaker 1  (45:58)
So yeah, my sense This is, I'm guessing this is a neural network right once inside this function. Okay? So another basics of hunger on it works work. 

Speaker 1  (46:13)
I just want to understand the implementation. I think possible yeah, so I'll allow you more about this feature. I mean it sounds like this is one of the main steps to decide what characteristic of this N by N matrix corresponds to the axes. 

Speaker 1  (46:30)
What characteristic will tell you whether you have a square symbol or a triangle symbol, or it's a failed symbol or an empty symbol. Because essentially one. 

Speaker 2  (46:41)
Okay? Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (46:44)
So without yeah, so those are things that I'll ask you about. You can tell me kind of what features you have decided on. And also check, you know, checking the literature. 

Speaker 1  (46:53)
I'm guessing some people over this relatively, you know. Our divided is a relatively strict port application, right? So much processing, wow. 

Speaker 1  (47:06)
So I'm guessing, maybe in the literature there are some comments about, you know, if you're one identify specific symbols, what is the best feature to do? 

Speaker 2  (47:16)
Oh, kiss I have him here. I got it fast, sir. 

Speaker 1  (47:20)
No friends are clear. Let me know if I'll ask you. None of this is not clear to me. 

Speaker 1  (47:24)
I want you to yeah, okay. Okay, so let's yeah, so let's let's, I'll ask you more about this. Let's just say, and then you're gonna start sharing the the The schedule and the online stuff and I'll try to also give up a little bit more on that so we can offer speaking the same language. 

Speaker 1  (47:47)
I don't get, does that make sense? Yes, and all kind of what is the? What is the goal? 

Speaker 2  (47:54)
Ah, yes, sir. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (47:56)
Yeah, so, right now. We won't do anything with the reason why I shared it with you. The articles is more so that you know, as you're looking at these catter plots, you have a sense of what they're telling you. 

Speaker 1  (48:13)
Boats, the bulk of this tool, right in essence this tool should be agnostic of what you're applying it to. Yes, we should just feed a scatter plot. And then you should be able to identify the axes their scale, whether it's linear or log, identify all the data points inside. 

Speaker 1  (48:33)
That's got our plot and then output csv files. Whispered, each day a series that you have in that scan. 

Speaker 2  (48:41)
Okay, okay. So 

Speaker 1  (48:43)
So that's the main thing that I wanted to do okay. After that right after we get our bus tool, I can do that. We can then talk about either extending it to other Datasets, like instead of scatterpods, we could do bar plots or curves inside a scatter plot because those have come up a lot. 

Speaker 1  (49:05)
And we can talk about doing a front end and the main tool right now that I've robust thing that ideally yeah would also give us an error of the measurement. It only needs to handle scatter plots. Another thing is for it. 

Speaker 1  (49:26)
So Just to think about right, you have a symbol idea. Typically, the center of the simple is, what gives you the data point, right? We got to find, I guess principle. 

Speaker 1  (49:38)
We've had to find a feature that identify a symbol, and then flies the center, okay. To get the report, okay, sir, yes. Yeah, sounds good. 

Speaker 1  (49:50)
So that I'm I'll send you. I'll write you to the slide channel and you can email me. Or whenever you know if you have any questions, feel free to send me a message. 

Speaker 1  (50:00)
Typically, which I'll reply sooner over slack. With some email, I'll try to reply soon. But sometimes it takes me a little bit and other than that. 

Speaker 1  (50:12)
I'll set up a meeting for Wednesday next week. 

Speaker 2  (50:15)
But, okay, sir. 

Speaker 1  (50:19)
So, that's good. 

